

Ahmad Aldali

Nationality: Syrian

**** (+964) 7518146994

Date of birth: 26/09/1995

Gender: Male

™ Email address: ahmadaldali88@gmail.com

Website: https://github.com/ahmadaldali

in LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ahmad-aldali

• Address: Erbil (Iraq)

ABOUT ME

A Software Engineer with more than 3 years of experience, and with strong desire of succeed. An ambitious person who try to get more experience in my profession, eager to learn new materials and skills. Amiable, persistent and competitive character.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

ZEUOR [20/07/2019 - Current]

- www.zeuor.com
 - 1. Planning, Developing and Testing Software.
 - 2. Manage product development minutiae.
 - 3. Communicate with other departments.

Teaching Assistant

Tishreen University, Faculty of Informatics Engineering [01/02/2019 - 13/03/2021]

City: Lattakia Country: Syria

Teaching Subjects:

- Information Security.
- Software Testing.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Master of Software Engineering and Information Systems.

Tishreen University, Faculty of Informatics Engineering [01/01/2019 - 13/03/2021]

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering Faculty

Tishreen University, Faculty of Informatics Engineering [01/09/2013 - 01/09/2018]

Final grade: 89.08%

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s):

Arabic

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

DIGITAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

PHP / Java / JavaScript / Dart / Python / C#

Web Development

Laravel Framework / Bootstrap / RESTful api / ASP.Net / HTML / CSS / JQuery / Vue JS / AJAX

Mobile Development

Flutter / Android SDK, Android Studio, Gradle / Telegram Bots

Desktop

C# Windows Form / JavaFX

Database

MySQL / SQLite / PL/SQL

Other

OOP / Design patterns / Git / Linux / Team Management & Team Work / Fast learner / Work Under Pressure / Leadership

PROJECTS

Flutter Projects

[09/2020 - Current]

- Corona Statistics.
- Who Will Win The Million.
- ZEUOR company application.

Queue Management System

[07/2019 - Current]

A full System that has contained 8 web applications so far.

You can find components of ZEUOR Queue Management System at: http://www.zeuor.com/PRODUCTS.html

https://demoglitt.zeuor.com/

https://democsa.zeuor.com/

https://demodsa.zeuor.com/

https://demoems.zeuor.com/

https://digitalpanel.zeuor.com/

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.zeuor.mobile

https://t.me/zeuor_demo_bot

Diamond Lion Pay

[03/2021 - 06/2021]

The Diamond Lion Mobile App allows customers and agents to purchase different telecom, gaming and internet cards within a click.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.alassad.AlassadPay

Diamond Lion website

[03/2021 - 06/2021]

Admin Panel.

https://thediamondlion.zeuor.com

Survey Website

[06/2019 - 09/2019]

Deploying surveys by teachers to collects information about courses from students.

Automatic Translation

[09/2017 - 07/2018]

An android app for Translation that takes a picture and extracts text from the image with OCR technology.

LSTM neural network does the Translation and then putting them back into the image.

Online Shopping Website

[03/2018 - 06/2018]

Building a small website for online shopping according to Systems Development Life Cycle (SDLC) including Planning, Analysis, Design, and Implementation.

Information Security Project

[10/2017 - 12/2017]

Coding for AES, DES, RC4 Algorithms.

Ethan Escape Game

[02/2017 - 06/2017]

3D Game was built with Unity and Blender.

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1KO3782FbRK-qQr4subxgcleJ9hVFcpeA/view

Video Search Using Image Query

[10/2016 - 12/2016]

We search a huge video database using an image to retrieve the video related to it. We segmented the video into frames then, we kept key frames in our database to compare it against the images used to search for stored videos, so that a video is indexed by several key frames.

CERTIFICATIONS

Certifications

Al Bassel Certificate for the Best Graduate by Tishreen University, IT Faculty, Ministry of Higher Education in (2015 - 2016).